<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
   <list>
      <que>Who is QuickEnrollment Inc.?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[QuickEnrollment was established in September 1999 and operates out of Markham, Ontario, Canada. QuickEnrollment Inc. provides online registration and payment solutions particularly, but not exclusively, to amateur and recreational sports organizations, their respective leagues and the tournaments they run. QE also provides development and integration services with third party solutions in order to further expand our comprehensive end-to-end solutions. Our expertise and knowledge in these areas have allowed us to offer our clients with the very best online registration and payment solutions in the industry. QuickEnrollment currently services a variety of amateur sports organizations across Canada.]]></ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>What products and services does QuickEnrollment currently offer?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[QE offers three main products and services:
      <br><br>
      <b>Registration Management Solutions (RMS):</b> We offer a full suite of online registration management solutions that enable organizations to provide their members with the utmost efficiencies and convenience while reducing administrative efforts by as much as 60%.
      <br><br>
      <b>Online Fee Collection Services (OFCS):</b> QE provides complete end-to-end logistics and services that enable your organization to fully automate your fee collection processes.
      <br><br>
      <b>Development and Integration (QE-Int):</b> QE has a long history of customizing solutions to meet our client’s needs. Whether it be customizing our RMS or OFCS offerings to address client’s needs or integrating our solutions with third party solutions, QE is committee to offering the most powerful, flexible and affordable solutions on the market.
      <br><br>
      For further detailed information on QE products and services, please see <a href="#/Products">OUR PRODUCTS</a>]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>How much does this service cost?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[The association you are registering for needs to become a client of QuickEnrollment for this service to be offered to the general membership. Price varies for many reasons; primarily depending on what system and/or services you are interested in using. Our pricing model is transaction-based and we DO NOT CHARGE ANY UPFRONT COSTS to the association. To find out more contact QuickEnrollment at <a href="mailto:info@quickenrollment.com">info@quickenrollment.com</a>
      <br><br>
      If you are a participant and like the added convenience of one of our QuickEnrollment solutions and your association is not offering this service to the membership, send us an email and we will get in touch with them immediately.
      <br><br>
      If you are an executive member of an association and you are interested in how QuickEnrollment can help you save time and money, contact us at <a href="mailto:info@quickenrollment.com">info@quickenrollment.com</a> to find out more.]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que> What is the relationship between QuickEnrollment and the association I am a member of?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[It is important to understand that QuickEnrollment PROVIDES online registration and payment services to your organization. We DO NOT manage the registration of your association, so, we cannot provide you with answers relating specifically to acceptance or rules surrounding registration. We simply PROVIDE online registration and payment services. However, feel free to contact us if you are having <b>technical difficulties</b> with the system. ]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
</faq>

