<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
   <list>
      <que>What is OFCS?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[O.F.C.S. stands for Online Fee Collection Services.
      <br><br>
        O.F.C.S. offers an end-to-end approach in all aspects of collecting fees over the internet.
      <br><br>
        Services provided include:
        <ul>
        <li>Credit card rate negotiations ensures the lowest rates in the market</li>
        <li>Merchant account acquisition logistics</li>
        <li>Credit Card processing integration with QE RMS or third party software</li>
        <li>Online credit card payment administrative tools and reporting</li>
        </ul>
        <br>
        For further detailed information on OFCS, please see OUR PRODUCTS- OFCS ]]></ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>What are the costs to collect fees online?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[All OFCS fees are charged to the organization monthly. The organization may incorporate OFCS charges within the fees charged to members. QE national volumes ensure that rates charged are the lowest available in the market. Please contact a QE representative at <a href="mailto:info@quickenrollment.com">info@quickenrollment.com</a> to discuss your needs and related fees. ]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>How do I sign up for OFCS?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[Contact us at <a href="mailto:info@quickenrollment.com">info@quickenrollment.com</a> to begin the process. We have automated and integrated much of the process from signing up with OFCS to obtaining an online merchant account to setting up your very own customized OFCS Control Centre. A QE representative will guide you each step of the way. ]]></ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>How does OFCS work?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[Once you have signed up with OFCS and provided all required information to be approved for an online merchant account, your merchant account provider will conduct all due diligence required to approve your account. Once approved, QE will set up and test your credit card processing module. You will also be setup with your own OFCS Control Centre that will allow you to view/print detailed integrated reporting, process refunds/voids and process a variety of credit card transactions. Once LIVE, you will be trained on all aspects of OFCS including functionalities of the OFCS Control Centre.
      <br><br>
      OFCS is automatically integrated with all of QE’s registration management solutions. We are also capable of integrating with third party solutions. During your registration process your member will select online credit card as a payment type. Once they submit their credit card information into our secure form, the fees will be processed and they will have an opportunity to view/print a receipt. One will also be automatically emailed to them. Payment details will be automatically updated in your OFCS and RMS reporting. Fees processed will be automatically deposited into your organization’s bank account within 1-2 business days. Your organization’s name will appear on the cardholder’s credit card statement.]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>What information am I able to access about fees processed?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[QE-OFCS is the first to integrate registration information to credit card processing information to bring you the most detailed, clear and concise reporting available in the market. Each organization has their own OFCS Control Centre, a web enabled administrative area containing many powerful functionalities and reporting tools. <a href="mailto:info@quickenrollment.com">Click here</a> for more information.]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>Can I process transactions unrelated to registration such as fundraising or merchandising?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[Yes. Any type of transaction may be processed through the Remote Terminal within the OFCS Control Centre.]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
   <list>
      <que>Can I process refunds?</que>
      <ans><![CDATA[Yes. You may process partial refunds or in full within your OFCS Control Centre. Credit Card information is not required in order to process a refund.]]>
      </ans>
   </list>
</faq>

